Ayush Paul

Developer & Designer





in ayushpaulllll (7) Ayushpaullll



Contact

- +91 90649 95568
- Banglore | Kolkata, India
- ayushpaul1111@gmail.com

About

I am an enthusiastic developer and designer, my passion has driven me to excel in multiple projects.

I've worked on several freelance projects for various firms as a developer and designer. Where I have always used a creative approach to problem-solving

Education

Schooling Rambhola High School 2013 - 2020

B.Tech in Computer Science Engineering Dayananda Sagar University 2020 - 2024

Portfolio

Here's my responsive and interactive website portfolio, built using React.js and Tailwind CSS.



Projects

Dayananda Library System | Frontend - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python Backend - My SQL Discription - Í was Front-end lead in this project. This is a real time project. Dayananda Sagar University and Dayananda Sagar Institutions is currently using this library system. (GitHub)

Bill Management System For Small Shops | Frontend - HTML, CSS, JS, Python Backend - My SQL Discription - A simple bill management system for small stores. (GitHub)

Experience

Graphic Designer (Drive) Skill Academia | West Bengal | 2021 - 2022 Tech - Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, premiere pro, Canva

Graphic Designer (Drive) Nincompoop | West Bengal | 2021 - 2022 Tech - Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, premiere pro, Canva

Front-end web development & Graphic and UI/UX Designer (Drive) Mediqueue | West Bengal | 2022 Tech - Html, Css, React.js, Figma Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, premiere pro, Canva

Professional Skills

HTML, CSS Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator React.js

Python Adobe XD

Adobe Premiere Pro Java **Adobe After Effect** C etc.



_ ayush_paul_



ayushpaul1111